(Howard:)Oh, yeah? How's that?
Two words: 3D printer.
But maybe it's three words.
No, hang on. Okay.
(Raj:)One word, a letter and a number,
and maybe a hyphen.
(Raj:)3D printer.
(Howard:)I have always wanted a 3D printer.
(Raj:)Of course you have.
They're an engineer's dream.
(Raj:)Anything you can design,
a 3D printer can make out of plastic.
(Howard:)Yeah, but they're so expensive.
(Raj:)Oh, come on, you deserve one.
(Raj:)You've worked hard to find a woman
who makes a lot of money.
(Howard:)Well, the prices have been coming down.
(Raj:)Oh, true.
They're practically giving them away.
(Raj:)You know, in exchange for money.
And we could make stuff we need
for work with it.
(Howard:)Prototypes of my CAD/CAM designs,
specialized tools.
(Raj:)Not to mention Malibu Koothrappali
and his totally bitching dream house.
(Howard:)We don't need
Malibu Koothrappali's dream house.
Really, smart guy? Where is he supposed
to park his sweet little Corvette?